Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Department for Professional Employees (DPE): "Professional Workers and Unions" Handbook, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Department for Professional Employees (DPE): Proposed Policy Statements, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Department for Professional Employees (DPE): Women's Project, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Doubleday Broadcasting Co., Inc.: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Doyle Dane Bernbach, Inc Advertising: Correspondence, General, 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Doyle Dane Bernbach, Inc Advertising: Jewish Philanthropies of Greater New York, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Earplay Radio Drama Production Center for Public Broadcasting: Program Information and Continuity Sheets, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation: Agreement with AFTRA, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META (Metropolitan Educational Television Association)], 1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1959 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1961 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1963 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Educational Television for the Metropolitan Area, Inc. [originally known as META], 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Emerson Radio Hall of Fame, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Environetics, Inc.: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): The AFL-CIO and Civil Rights [Booklet], 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - EEO: Binder, Survey, Joint SAG-AFTRA Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Carsey-Werner Company, Minority Report, Network Contract EEO Summary, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): "The Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions" [Booklet], 1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Coalition on Women and the Budget, "Inequality of Sacrifice: The Impact of the Reagan Budget on Women", Mar 1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Binder, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Committee Meeting, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Complaints and Related Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Complaints and Related Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Conference, General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Conference, Walker, Terry Binder, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC), Report on Women's Activities, AFL-CIO Civil Rights Committee Meeting, Apr 1985 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC) SAG/AFTRA Conference Report, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC) SAG/AFTRA Conference Report, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Commission (EEOC) SAG/AFTRA Conference Report, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee Binder, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee Binder, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee, Correspondence, Minority Hiring, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee, General (Meeting Summaries and Minutes), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee, Meeting, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Committee, Meeting, Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, Agenda, Legislation and Related Material, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, Correspondence and Related Material, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, Information Folder, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, News Clippings and Related Materials, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, SAG/AFTRA, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Expenses, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Information, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Congressional Black Caucus, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Correspondence, General, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): EEO-1, Petition for Amendment, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): FCC Petition, No. 18244, Aug 1970 - Mar 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): FCC Petition, No. 18244, Apr 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): FCC Petition, No. 18244, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): General, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Joint Statement of Policy, 1963, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Labor Relations Reporter, "Opinion Announced May 1, 1989", and Related Materials (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Legislation, S. 577, H.R. 315, H.R. 1432, S. 54, S. 1511, H.R. 1267, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, Hollywood, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, Hollywood, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, Hollywood, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, New York, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, New York, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Lists, Minority Performers on CBS Shows, New York, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Memo, Gender Survey, Wolff, Sanford, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Employment, Afro-Asian Artists' Register, British Actors Equity, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Employment, Reports (ABC, CBS, NBC), Correspondence, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, ABC Entertainment, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Act III Television Venture, "Jody and the News," "The Storyteller," "Sunday Dinner", 1990 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "All My Children", 1988-1991 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Bell-Phillip TV Productions, "The Bold and the Beautiful", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Buena Vista Entertainment, General, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Columbia Pictures, "227", 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Columbia Pictures, "Family Medical Center", 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Columbia Pictures, Sunday Funnies, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Columbia Pictures, "Who's the Boss", 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Columbia Pictures, "The Young and the Restless", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Dangerous Women", 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Days of Our Lives", 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, EB Productions, "Superior Court", 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, ELP Communications, "Who's the Boss," "227," "Married... with Children", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Employment Status Reports, Columbia Pictures, Jul 1990 - Dec 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Minority Report, E.O.B. Productions, "The War Room", 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Fresh Prince of Bel-Air", 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "General Hospital", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Generations," NBC Productions, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "A Girl's Life", 1989 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "The Golden Girls", 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Jackee", 1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Julie Brown: The Show", 1989 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Kate & Allie", 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Loving", 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Married...with Children", 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, NBC Productions Inc., "Chip and Pepper", 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, NBC Productions Inc., General, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Minority Report, "One Life to Live", 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Roseanne", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Santa Barbara", 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, "Saved by the Bell," NBC Productions Inc., Franco Bario, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Statistics, "The Bold and the Beautiful", 1988 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Statistics, "The Bold and the Beautiful", 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Tudor Television, Inc., "I'm Home", 1990 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Minority Report, Twentieth Century Fox Film Corp., "Mrs. Belvedere," "Sister Kate", 1990 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Articles, Media, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan 1990 - Feb 1990 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Correspondence and Related Materials, Mar 1990 - Apr 1990 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Correspondence and Related Materials, May 1990 - Jun 1990 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Legislation Discussed, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): National Conference, SAG/AFTRA, Television, Radio Recorded Commercials Contract, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Network Database, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Network Database, Problems (Includes Copy of 1991 Ross Reports), 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Network Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Atlanta, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Boston, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Chicago, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Cincinnati/Columbus/Dayton, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Cincinnati/Columbus/Dayton, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Cincinnati/Columbus/Dayton, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Denver, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire [82-CVR-39], Florida (Folder 1 of 2), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire [82-CVR-39], Florida (Folder 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Kansas City/Omaha, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, New York, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, San Diego, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, Seattle, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire Statistics, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire, St. Louis, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Questionnaire [82-CVR-39], Washington DC, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): The Sensitive Listener of the 1980's [Equal Rights Committee] (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Statistics, 1988-1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Statistics, Daytime Serials, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Statistics, Los Angeles, Minority Report, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Statistics, Network Negotiations, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Statistics, New York Soaps, 1988-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Stereotyping, Surveys of Minorities and the Disabled on CBS and NBC, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Study, Database (D-Base), 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Title VII, Women in the Work Place, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - European Committee of Trade Unions in Arts, Mass Media and Entertainment (EGAKU), 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO): Training and Educational Funds, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Executives: Conaway, Donald F, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Executives: Dowell, Reginald, Correspondence, 1964 - 1967, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Executives: Farrell, Reed, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Executives: Groot, Kenneth, Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Executives: Hall, John C., Correspondence, Coleman, Patricia (Assistant to Hall), 1978-1993 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Executives: Heller, George, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Executives: Heller, George, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Executives: Heller, George, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Executives: Heller, George, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Executives: Kocin, Harold, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence [Contains Original Signature of Claude Rains], 1963 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Executives: Lewis, Irving, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Executives: McKee, Alex, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Executives: McKee, Alex, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Executives: Nelson, William H., Assistant Executive Secretary, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Executives: Reel, A. Frank (National Executive Secretary), Correspondence, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Correspondence, 1985 - Aug 1987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Correspondence, Sep 1987 - Dec 1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Read File, Memorandums, Jan 1989 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Read File, Feb 1989 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Read File, Mar 1989 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Read File, Apr 1989 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Executives: Walker, Terry, Self Pay Health Insurance, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), "Communications and Society" Aspen Institute, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), "Computerized Manufacturing Automation", 1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), "Computerized Manufacturing Automation" Summary, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence (Blackmer, Sidney), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, Jan 1979 - Sep 1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, Oct 1979 - Dec 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, Storecasting, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Correspondence, Testimonial Dinner, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Datebooks, 1984, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), "Videocassettes The Systems The Market The Future", 1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Executives: Wolff, Sanford I. (Bud), Work Travel, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Executives: York, Bruce A., Articles, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Executives: York, Bruce A., Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Executives: York, Bruce A., Correspondence, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Fairness Doctrine [Bills S.2 and H.R.2189], 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Federal Broadcasting Company: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 27)